Hello hi guys welcome to our latest video
and in this video we are going to discuss the
best insurance talk which is
listed in the Indian stock market and we will also discuss
what is the operation team of insurance
in India and whether it can become the next big
thing for the next five to ten years.
According to the reports,
Insurance talk of insurance sector
is standing in that space where our
Indians who were standing from private banks,
in Twenty20, let us
try to do a very good job of private banks, so we will
answer the question in this video,
so let us see the insurance industry
in India, how many products were there, that
thing was that tips were subscribed and
before that if you had the government, but its
third party insurance policy holders, they had a lot of
insurance
in the market and they felt that they should have a level
playing field, if I talk about
life insurance then you do a lot of
online insurance which is the global average of
3538 less, the global average of US, western
countries in Europe, all these people have even more than that, Alien
Life and Life Insurance Scheme which
you  It shows how many opportunities there are
in India right now. Insurance is done in India.
Insurance premium subscription 2002
insurance. If you look at the insurance premium
according to the population of the country, if
20 and if you subscribe to our festivals
and
add sugar, then it will take a lot of time for us to reach the growth
prospects of four, five, six
standards.
This is a very good option for the
insurance industry in India. If you look at the
market share, the bid to increase the percentage is 215 present and leave for the next 325. So you can see how much growth runway the insurance industry has right now. If I talk about the market share in general insurance, you have
public general insurance, they have
61.34 private general insurance,
they have 61.34 versus the entire
application that
private
insurance has.
In private insurance, the top companies that have the
highest market share are ICICI
Lombard, Spiegel, and Bajaj Allianz.
If I talk about life insurance, then there are more companies
in life insurance.  In the lesser story,
public general insurance which is LIC,
bike insurance centre and share and private
insurance Varun are running at 14% and if
you look at the private insurance then the
major players are SBI
and ICICI Life Insurance is
also called Quality Products. So now let's
discuss about stocks, there is a
very soft company, its name is
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company, let's see a little about the company, then the
company was basically started, it was a joint
venture of ICICI Bank and
Fairfax Financial Holdings,
both of them because private companies, then they
commented their operations and it was listed
in the Indian stock market
on 27th September 2017, the company offers various
insurance like Rawal, I am also in the health and motor
segment, if you look at it, then the
company has issued 26.2 million
policies in this period and has settled over 1.8 million
policies on March 30 and you could get more, the
best thing is that they were just visited,
so it took them only two years, so  It is the
largest private sector non-life
insurance in India and the opposite which has been
taken till date, the one which has the
highest market share is ICICI
Lombard General Insurance. If we look at the
fundamentals of the private sector, the
market profit is strong. The current price is
different from 2012. The face value of the
insurance and ROC, both are
20% plus, which is a very good thing. If
you look at it, the profit is 108%. If you
look at it on the other side, both are doing very
well and the
promoter holding is 50% plus. Debt to
equity, if you look at it, is zero to zero
six, which is a very good number. If
I talk about the appeal, then if you
look at the series, it has been falling every year.
This year it has reduced a bit, but
overall, if you look at it, 11 years ago, the
operating profit is 193 crores in 2018. If
you look at it, it is 4258 crores from 229 crores.  It has been done
and if I talk about net profit, it used to be
124 crores in half an hour,
then - I got angry, but after that
you will see a very good growth
and the net profit has reached 48738 crores. If you
look at the different, then there is an FD account, a very
broking company is out on 35 pres.
If you talk about the balance sheet, then
look at this, 381 crores have grown, the
boring was nothing earlier, but some
time ago, 20 crores were Rs.45 crores, the
boring is stagnant, this is nothing
special, otherwise if you see, they were also Chinese
cents, their boring is nothing special,
if you look at the share holding pattern, then the
most important thing in this down phase is
that even if the promoters
reduce their shares a little, they keep on
taking, then you can see a good thing in it that
you are taking interest,
if you see, it has become 108
from 8.5, just look at it, it is 11.6  That is a very
good thing, the amount of data that those who sell ads have on the
devices they use is more than what
we have. And again, retailers do
n't have that much idea. So, if you see, if they
increase
their share every quarter, then this is a very good
point, public, see, your savings
start on 28th, sir, spring has come, and all the
strong investors have maturity
and shareholding.
If we look at the music and lights of this company tomorrow morning, then the
two most important
numbers are that from 508
to 22, ICICI Lombard's
profit after tax is
growing at 23.8%. And I will tell you a more
interesting thing than this, the overall
industry has shown an increase in this time frame. So,
wherever there is
competition,
their profit compounding time is going negative. If you keep looking at it, the
net profit is 2300. The
main reason for this is that ICICI
Lombard stays away from those segments.
Where they see high loss rescuers,
they try to target those
segments. For example, I'll give you an
example: in the past two years,
they aggressively grew the fire
insurance sector. While they have already made a
complete exit from group insurance,
which is
70% of the total, the product portfolio
student feels that whatever little interest there may be, they can get out of it. The
profit from celery is
made a part of their product portfolio. The
second point is ICICI
Bank's network. They have been very well-
organized. Their entire distribution
network is the brand of June. They
help IAS Bond a lot. If we
talk about folding the motor, rough
weather, Maryam, whatever they have, they have been very
successful. Because of ICICI Bank's
network, Bhairav ​​selling etc. becomes
very easy. And from ID,
you know, the bigger the bank is, the Durga
overall network, it will help a lot in this and make it
long.
If I talk about the crucial point for growing this rapidly,
it is the high quality of Android. Like
you know that in banks with 100MB of left, where
asset underwriting is a very important
thing if you want to build a high quality loan book,
then high
quality liability underwriting in this channel is
very important in the insurance sector
and that is a very
positive thing. Soon, the underwriting will be done in IAS body and
it is of very
good quality and if you see that
if you want to know
how good their underwriting quality is, then in the past
tests, such events on the side, from
etc., there is a lot of loss in it
and those who have term insurance like them have to do it
on a very high amount, even then
if you see,
their share of loss is much less than their market share. In such cut off
profit events, this tells you
that the underwriting is of very
high quality.
If you look at the full point tomorrow morning, their focus is
very much on technology, so
this  What are you doing at Unlimited?
Using Machine Learning Principle Blitz, they
are collecting consumer behavior data so that a consumer can get a post
like solution, which can mute the consumer's
expectations very well.
Apart from that, let me tell you,
these people are in Robotic Process Automation,
which you are using, the time of consumer
is setting, song code generation to follow
C. In this, he has to take the level very low, due to
which the experience of the said youth has become much better, so by doing this
directly,
logging in to the contact, it is very good
and we are giving a very good experience to the consumer. The
last point if I talk about, it is
virtual office interior three
and care for all times to analyze, get rid of two-three
years, so if I talk about 1st year, 3rd year
for town, then
opening complete offices etc. there where there
is not much demand right now, there will
not be much pain, friend,
basically what should be done, duty airplane
Set up virtual offices in tier-4 towns and
whatever demand there is for health
insurance, even for medical shops,
whatever that demand is, you can
meet it.
If I talk about the biggest set of insurance in these cities tomorrow morning, the
biggest one is the environment, that is, meta
properties, for example, if you suppose
insurance has started in case of terrorist attack or terrorism,
and if unfortunately such a
time happens in that, then the
general insurance companies have to give a very
profitable and invaluable salute,
but if I look at the third, then climate
change, if you see, climate change is
global warming, due to that, many things happen, there is a
draft, if you see,
friends, there are untimely rains, due to
which if you see, then the health care in the
subsequent makes a difference, the
biggest difference is that of crop
insurance, and in that, as
I told you, I had left
that entire segment some time ago after returning from ICL, that
they had a very loss-making
secret, this could happen if I  If I talk about the third third, then
it is epidemically endemic,
as you can see right now that
due to 2019, the companies which do health insurance,
they started having to launch a
big launch at some time
because they are having to sell out a lot of money,
so the people who used to get insurance
from the internet and those who had to
stay in hospitals etc., there has been a lot of
expenditure, due to this the general
insurance company has
200, if I tell you in the end, it seems to me that it is the biggest
insurance company in the country, it has a very fundamentally strong, if you see it from your profit, then it is also very strong in the last 5s, glass typing and 30, the market leader is no life insurance, but
look at its place and this is the market
share of June that year, it is continuously increasing, so
if you feel that there is a lot of growth in the insurance sector
in the last fifteen years, then
you
can do some research about this topic and if you
like it then you can invest, but leave no stone unturned.
First of all,
consult your financial advisor.
Like the video. Dil Se Only For
Education Focus, so that I can store data for you about
what is happening in the insurance industry
and how well ICICI Lombard is doing in it.
Tiger Shroff's